Let's eat!
（一同）いただきまーす
Yum!
（マコ）おいしー
Your croquettes are as
awesome as ever, Mom!
（又郎(またろう)）いやあ 相変わらず
母ちゃんのコロッケはうめえな
（ガッツ）ワン！
Yeah! When it comes to deep-frying mystery ingredients, you're the best in Japan, dear!
（薔薇蔵(ばらぞう)）
おう 何だかわからないもの
油で揚げさせたら日本一だよ
The trick is to chop everything finely and mix in some potatoes.
（好代(すくよ)）何でも細かく刻んで—
じゃがいもに混ぜちゃうのが
コツなんですよ
（流子(りゅうこ)）
う〜ん　おばさんのコロッケ
確かにうまいっす
Your croquettes
really are great, ma'am!
I'm glad you think so.
（好代）よかった
遠慮しなくていいからね
Please, eat all you like.
Oh, I'm already full.
でも もういっぱい
Thanks for the meal.
ごちそうさまです
If you're done eating, Ryuuko, the bath is drawn and ready.
（好代）流子ちゃん ご飯済んだら
お風呂 沸いてるわよ
Oh. Sure.
（流子）あっ はい
The bath?!
（薔薇蔵･又郎）お風呂？
（流子）フフッ
（鮮血(せんけつ)）どうした？ 何がおかしい
What is it? What's so funny?
Lively meals are a great thing.
（流子）
にぎやかな食事っていいもんだな
Mom died when I was little,
（流子）母さんは早くに死んで—
and Dad sent me off to a boarding school.
父さんは私を
寄宿舎付きの学校に入れた
So I never had any family meals before.
だから
家族と一緒の食事は知らない
I always thought
that was just how it was.
そんなもんだと思ってたけど
But now I see that eating with the
whole family makes even the food taste better.
こうやって家族みんなで
にぎやかに食べるご飯って—
おいしいもんなんだな
...However...
って思うが…
I could do without the
damn peeping toms!
（薔薇蔵）ぐあっ
（流子）のぞきは いらーん！
We're sorry!
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
（薔薇蔵･又郎）ごめんなさーい
MANKANSHOKU
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
EPISODE 7
A LOSER I CAN'T HATE
This is a world tailored to someone's whims and fancies
dareka ga katteni kimeta readymade na
I'll break free of its shackles
kyou wo nugisutete
RYUUKO
MATOI
And sprint toward my goal
hadashi de hashitte iku
Even if I lose my way
machigattatte
GAMAGOORI IRA
SANAGEYAMA UZU
JAKUZURE NONON
INUMUTA HOUKA
Or trip and fall
korondatte
INUMUTA HOUKA
MANKANSHOKU FAMILY
Those wounds will still create
surimuita itami mo
MANKANSHOKU
MAKO
MIKISUGI
AIKUROU
KINAGASE
TSUMUGU
An original future for me
original na ashita ni naru
KIRYUUIN
SATSUKI
I hold my destiny in my own hands
tsukiageta kono te ni nigirishimeta
And it shines ever so brightly
chikai ga hikari ni natte
So until the day I reach you
itsuka kimi ni todoku sono shunkan made
I don't have the time to sit around crying
naiteru hima nante nai kara
My burning passion pours out from within me
hamidashite shimatta atsui omoi ga
And shines like a star in the night sky
yozora de kagayaki dasu
I think I now understand
umarete kita imi ga
Why I was born
wakatta ki ga shita
I'll make all of my dreams come true
negaigoto wa zenbu kono te de
With my own hands
kanaeru
That looks good!
（流子）うまそー
Time for lunch!
（マコ･流子）いただきまーす
Ka-swoosh!
（内藤(ないとう)）シャキーン！
Matoi Ryuuko!
（内藤）纏(まとい)流子 お前は
この投げナイフ部部長—
Jack Naitou, president of the
Knife Throwing Club, will take you down!
ジャック内藤が倒す
KNIFE THROWING CLUB PRESIDENT JACK NAITOU
You've got some nerve,
（流子）てめえ！ よくもマコの
おふくろさんの弁当を！
ruining the lunch that
Mako's mom made for me!
You'll pay for that!
許せねえ！
Life Fiber Synchronize, Godrobe Senketsu!
人衣(じんい)一体 神衣(かむい)鮮血
GODROBE
SENKETSU
Ka-swoosh!
（内藤）シャキーン！
（内藤の悲鳴）
（流子）戦維(せんい)喪失
Thread Stripper!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
（マコ）あ〜ん ウフッ
（陰三郎(かげさぶろう)）ヘヘヘ… やるな
Impressive!
The one who will defeat you is me,
（陰三郎）お前をやるのは
南京玉すだれ部部長—
NANJING LILY CLUB PRESIDENT
Nanjing Lily Club President
Kagero Kagesaburou!
NANJING LILY CLUB PRESIDENT
KAGERO KAGESABUROU
この陽炎(かげろう)陰三郎なのだ！
（陰三郎の悲鳴）
（流子）戦維喪失
Thread Stripper.
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
TIGHTROPE WALKING CLUB
PRESIDENT WATARI MASUYO
（益代(ますよ)）オーホッホッホ
私は綱渡り部部長…
TIGHTROPE WALKING CLUB
PRESIDENT WATARI MASUYO
I am president of the
Tightrope Walking Club!
TIGHTROPE WALKING CLUB
PRESIDENT WATARI MASUYO
（益代の悲鳴）
（流子）戦維喪失
Thread Stripper!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
A Knife Throwing Club, a Nanjing Lily Club,
and a Tightrope Walking Club?
（流子）
投げナイフに南京玉すだれに
綱渡りって 何なんだよ
What's with all these
ultra-specific clubs?
そこまで細分化した部活動は
Oh, those guys used to be
the Acrobatics Club.
（マコ）ああ
元は みんな曲芸部だよ
分かれたのは
流子ちゃんのせいだよ
They split up because of you.
Because of me?
（流子）私の？
Yep. If someone beats you,
（マコ）そう　流子ちゃん倒したら
一気に三つ星になれるから
they'll jump up to Three-Star status.
でも 部長にならないと—
But since you can't get a Two-Star
Ultima Uniform unless you're a club president,
二つ星極制服が
手に入らないから—
they all founded new clubs
and are gunning for you.
みんな新しい部を作って
流子ちゃんを狙ってるんだよ
Say what?
何！
星が増えれば
いい暮らしができるからね
More stars means a better life.
They're all desperate.
みんな必死だよ
Man, this academy's system
is seriously messed up.
（流子）
ったく やらしいシステムだな
この学園は
Hey, hang on! If that's how it works, then...
待てよ だったら…
Fight
Club
What are you playing at, Matoi?
（蟇郡(がまごおり)）何のつもりだ 纏
You have eyes, don't you?
Fight
Club
見てわからないか？
喧嘩(けんか)部の旗揚げだ
I'm starting a Fight Club.
Fight
Club
Quit screwing with us.
Fight
Club
（蟇郡）ふざけたマネを
Fight
Club
You're the ones who are
screwing with me!
（流子）ふざけてるのは そっちだ
Fight
Club
You're forcing students to start stupid clubs to go after me.
Fight
Club
くだらない部活 作って
私を狙わせてるんだろう？
Fight
Club
So I'm gonna do the same.
Fight
Club
だったら こっちだって
やってやるよ
Fight
Club
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT MATOI RYUUKO
Fight
Club
Say hello to the Fight Club President,
the great Matoi Ryuuko!
Fight
Club
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT MATOI RYUUKO
喧嘩部部長 纏流子様だ
Fight
Club
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT MATOI RYUUKO
Fight
Club
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT MATOI RYUUKO
Fight
Club
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT MATOI RYUUKO
Fight
Club
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT MATOI RYUUKO
Fight
Club
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT MATOI RYUUKO
Fight
Club
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT MATOI RYUUKO
Fight
Club
Do you seriously think that a
club like that will be approved?
そんな部活動が
認められると思うか？
I'll approve this "Fight Club"!
（皐月(さつき)）その喧嘩部 認めよう
There she goes again, looking down at us peasants from on high.
また 高い所から見下ろしやがって
Are you trying to integrate
into my system, Matoi?
（皐月）私のシステムに
自ら組み込まれるか 纏
Moron!
バカ！ お前のシステムごと
打ち砕いてやるっつってんだよ
I'm gonna make your precious system fall to pieces around you!
フッ 面白い　せいぜい
飲み込まれないようにな
How amusing.
Try your best not to
let it get the better of you.
Just you watch.
（流子）見てな すぐに
てめえのその口 割らせてやる！
I'll get my answers
out of you before you know it!
Very well. Let's begin the paperwork!
（蟇郡）では 事務手続きに入る
Fight
Club
You switch gears real fast, don'tcha?
Fight
Club
（流子）切り替え 早いね
Fight
Club
Lady Satsuki has spoken.
（蟇郡）皐月様のご意志だ
逆らうわけにはいかん
Fight
Club
I must abide by her decision.
Matoi! I assume you will be
president of this "Fight Club", then?
纏 喧嘩部の部長は
貴様でいいのだな？
Yeah. And I don't need
no Ultima Uniform.
おう　極(ごく)制服はいらないよ
この神衣があるからな
I already got my Godrobe.
Understood.
（蟇郡）了解した
Report
Club presidents are to submit
a club activity log every Friday.
部長は毎週金曜日に
活動報告書を提出してもらう
At the end of each month, expenses are settled and expense applications for the next month are filed.
また月末には経費精算と
翌月の経費申請
You must also file a club room request form,
club member organization chart,
そして部室使用申請書に
部員構成表に—
家族構成表の以上が必要だ
and list of club member families.
You are also required to attend Club President Council meetings, which are held every morning at 7am!
そして毎朝７時から開かれる
部長会議に出席のこと
遅刻は許さん
Tardiness will not be tolerated!
Um, my friend Mankanshoku Mako here says she'll be club president!
あっ 部長はこいつが
満艦飾(まんかんしょく)マコがやるって
That was so, so mean!
（マコ）
ひどいよ ひどいよ 流子ちゃん
勝手に部長にするなんて
How could you make me
president like that, Ryuuko?
Everything's set up.
（流子）話はつけた
喧嘩部の活動目的はケンカ
The Fight Club is all about fighting.
When I beat the other club presidents,
（流子）
あたしがほかの部長を倒せば
部活の成果が認められて—
the club's achievements
will be recognized,
and your reputation will skyrocket!
マコの評価がガンガン上がるんだ
暮らしも楽になるだろう
It'll also improve our
living situation, right?
But I can't! I can't!
でも 無理 無理 無理 無理
部長なんて無理〜！
I just can't be a club president!
Prepare yourself!
（流子）たのもー！
I'm Matoi Ryuuko from the Fight Club!
喧嘩部所属 纏流子だ
Folk Dance Club President,
Okurahama Maimu!
FOLK DANCE
CLUB PRESIDENT
OKURAHAMA
MAIMU
I'm here to take your Ultima Uniform!
お前の極制服 狩らせてもらう
Suits me fine!
（舞夢(まいむ)）上等よ
返り討ちにしてやるわ
Prepare to have the
tables turned, sister!
High Speed Mayim Mayim!
（舞夢）高速マイムマイム！
Let's dance!
受けてみなさい
It'll take more than this lame dance to defeat the mighty Ryuuko.
（流子）こんな なまくらダンスで
倒される流子様じゃねえぞ
Be-sasson!
（舞夢たち）えいさっさ
（流子）うっ…
Be-sasson!
（舞夢たち）えいさっさ
（流子）うっ…
（流子）フン！
Thread Stripper!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
（流子）よっしゃ！
じゃんじゃん いくぞー！
Oh, yeah! Let's keep going!
Fight
Club
（マコ）おーう
Fight
Club
...'Kay...
Fight
Club
（流子）フン！
MORNING
ASSEMBLY
（蟇郡）フン！
（マコ）うっ
Pottery Club Presidents,
the Three Touki Brothers!
（陶器三兄弟(とうきさんきょうだい)）
陶芸部部長 陶器三兄弟
POTTERY CLUB
PRESIDENTS
THE THREE
TOUKI
BROTHERS
Taste our clay psychokinesis!
食らえ 粘土力(ねんどうりき)！
Thread Stripper!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
（マコ）お〜 又郎
マンション すごいよ！
What a lovely view.
（好代）いい景色ね
マンションよ お父さん
We finally have a condo, honey.
（又郎）イエーイ
（マコ）すごい！ ここ
（好代）いい景色ね
マンションよ お父さん
（マコ）すごいよ〜
（薔薇蔵）そうだな
診療所まである
It's a fine place.
It even has a clinic.
（又郎）メンションだ
メンション〜
（薔薇蔵）そうだな
診療所まである
Front-ALLEY DOCTOR
MANKANSHOKU
But what the heck is a "front-alley doctor"?
“表やみいしゃ”って何なんだよ
Front-ALLEY DOCTOR
MANKANSHOKU
In this town, if Kiryuuin okays it, it's all good!
鬼龍院(きりゅういん)がＯＫならＯＫなんだよ
この町じゃ
（ガッツ）ウオ〜 ガッツ
（マコ）うわ〜
すごいよ すごいよ〜
Oh, wow! Oh, wow!
It even has a bathtub
that's inside the house!
お風呂だって家の中にあるし
It's got a fully automatic
washing machine!
全自動洗濯機よ
There's even a dishwasher!
食器洗い機まであるわ
（又郎）うっほー 冷房だ
An air conditioner!
And there's one in every room!
しかも 全部の部屋に！
こいつは たまげた！
水洗便所…
This is incredible!
It's a flush toilet, guys!
Ryuuko! This one's our room!
流子ちゃん
ここ私たちの部屋だよ
Yay! Three cheers for being a One-Star!
やったー！ 一つ星万歳！
I know she said your lifestyle is tied to how well your club does,
部活の成果が
生活に結び付くとはいえ—
but I can't believe they're
this in-your-face about it.
こんなに露骨だとは…
Let's eat!
（満艦飾一家）いただきまーす
No more mystery croquettes!
（好代）何だかわからない
コロッケじゃないよ
メンチカツだよ
These are genuine mincemeat cutlets!
100% mincemeat cutlets,
made from a ground blend of meat
ちゃんと牛と豚の
合いびき肉で作った—
that came from actual cows and pigs!
肉100パーセントのメンチカツだよ
（ガッツ）ハワワー…
It's delicious! It's so delicious!
（又郎）う… うめえ うめえよ
To think that we'd actually
...be able to live like this...
（薔薇蔵）まさか俺たちに
こんな暮らしができるなんて
Thank you, Mako and Ryuuko!
ありがとう！ マコ 流子ちゃん
全部２人のおかげだ
We owe it all to you two!
いや 礼なんかいいっすよ
Oh, you don't need to thank us!
Just knowing that you guys are
happy is thanks enough for me!
おじさんたちが喜んでくれるなら
あたしは それで…
Yeah!
You're still gonna pull this
peeping tom crap here?!
（流子）それでも
のぞくんかーい！
（薔薇蔵）うわー
（又郎）それとこれとは別だい
Location has nothing to do with it!
What he said!
（薔薇蔵）まったく
Their eyes were positively sparkling!
（マコ）みんなキラキラしてる
こんな生活ウソみたい
This life is almost too good to be true.
Ryuuko, I'm gonna work real hard to
be the best Fight Club president I can be.
流子ちゃん 私 頑張るよ
喧嘩部部長として
I know you will.
I'll leave all that to you.
ああ よろしくな
（愛善坊(あいぜんぼう)）ハーハッハッハ
I'm so glad you've come, Matoi Ryuuko!
FIGHT
CLUB
（愛善坊）よく来たな 纏流子
You're up against the Ping Pong Club President, Fuguhara Aizenbou!
PING PONG
CLUB
PRESIDENT
AIZENBO
FUGUHARA
...Let's see how you handle...
受けてみろ！
my Flaming Serve!
炎のサーブ〜
Thread Stripper!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
REPORT
Folk Dance Club
Swimming
Club
Pottery
Ping Pong
Club
Origami
Tightrope Walking Club
Knife Throwing Club
Nanjing Lily Club
Let's fight!
（追手(おって)）ゆくぞ！
ORIGAMI
CLUB
PRESIDENT
OTTE
TATAMU
You shall face the Origami Club
President, Otte Tatamu!
Thread Stripper!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
Given the circumstances,
（マコ）というわけで 喧嘩部の
待遇アップを要求するのであります
I hereby propose that the Fight Club's standard of living be raised!
I'm gonna do whatever I can to make sure everyone's eyes stay sparkling!
（マコ）キラキラした生活は
絶対 私が守り抜く！
Ugh, French cuisine again?
（又郎）またフランス料理かよ
Oh, you're going out, dear?
（好代）あら？
あなた お出かけですか？
（薔薇蔵）ああ
医師会の会合があってな
Indeed. I have a Medical Association meeting.
Oh, I see.
（好代）そうなんですか
あっ この間のダイヤのネックレス
買ってもよろしいかしら？
Would it be all right if I bought that
diamond necklace I showed you the other day?
（薔薇蔵）ああ あれはいい
お前によく似合う
Of course. I rather like that necklace. It looks wonderful on you.
（又郎）闇医者が
どんな医師会だよ
What kind of Medical Association do back-alley doctors have?
Matarou.
（好代）又郎
（又郎）おっと いっけねー
Damn, I almost forgot!
I got invited to a
friend's birthday party.
（又郎）
俺 ダチの誕生パーティーに
呼ばれてたんだ
I'm going out as well.
（好代）私も出かけるわ
流子ちゃん ゆっくり食べてね
Enjoy your dinner, Ryuuko.
Oh, sure.
（流子）あっ はい
I'm sorry. The Club President
Council meeting ran late.
（マコ）ごめんね
部長会議が伸びちゃって
Huh? Where is everyone?
あれ？ みんなは？
I guess they're all busy
doing their own thing.
それぞれ 忙しいみたいだ
Oh, I see.
そっかそっか
それじゃあ 流子ちゃん
Okay then, Ryuuko, once you're done,
食事終わったら
トレーニングルームで筋トレね
head to weight training
in the gymnasium.
You have a packed schedule
both tomorrow and the day after that.
あしたも あさっても
スケジュール ハードだよ
Huh?
I really must say, though,
（マコ）でもホント
こんな大きな屋敷に住めて—
being able to live in a
huge mansion like this,
right in the lap of luxury,
ぜいたくな暮らしができて
あたしたちホントにキラキラだよね
is enough to make anyone's
eyes sparkle with joy, isn't it?
Let's do everything we can
to keep this lifestyle, okay?
絶対に この暮らし守ろうね
Um... Sure.
I'm gonna go to bed, okay?
（マコ）じゃあ 先に寝るね
Sure.
All right, Ryuuko!
（マコ）さあ 流子ちゃん
この体育館の全員が相手よ
You're going to fight
every single person in this gym!
What?
（女子レスリング部員たち）
おりゃー
Seriously?
I am the Fight Club President,
Mankanshoku Mako!
（拡声器:マコ）
喧嘩部部長 満艦飾マコである
Club member Matoi Ryuuko
hereby challenges all of you to battle!
我が部の纏流子が
お前たちにケンカを挑む
Let's have a good, clean fight!
いざ尋常に！ 勝負 勝負！
Bring me every last
drop of sake you've got!
（薔薇蔵）この店の酒
全部 持ってこい！
I'd like all the Dom Perignon
you have, please!
ドンペリ全部 入れてちょうだい
（男性たち）フゥ〜
（流子）プハ〜
Good fight, Ryuuko.
（マコ）お疲れお疲れ 流子ちゃん
Let's head out to the
field for your next few.
んじゃ 次は
グラウンドに行ってみようか
（流子）ハァ〜
Nice chocolates you have here.
（又郎）ここにあるチョコ
全部 買い取りだ！
I'll take them all!
（店員）ありがとうございます
Thank you, sir.
（女の子たち）キャー
（又郎）ウフン
（ガッツ）ガッツ ワオーン
（雌犬たち）アオーン
（アメフト部員）フン！
（流子）くっ…
（アメフト部員）どりゃ！
ハァ ハァ…
What right do you have
to be here, lowly student?
（蛇崩(じゃくずれ)）なんで劣等生が
そこにいるの？
Our club's achievements
should answer that for you.
部活動の結果ですわ
That's the best part
of Honnouji Academy.
この本能字(ほんのうじ)学園のいいところ
それは実力が全てということでしょ
Personal ability is
everything, remember?
（蛇崩）
ヤツらをのさばらせておいて
いいんですか？ 皐月様
Are you going to let these people have their way, Lady Satsuki?
（蟇郡）
このままでは 纏と満艦飾が
生徒会の中枢に入ってきます
Unless something is done,
Matoi and Mankanshoku will become
part of the Student Council's inner circle.
That just means anyone they beat to
get here wasn't qualified to begin with.
（皐月）倒された者は 所詮
そこまでの器だったということだ
Let me fight her again.
（猿投山(さなげやま)）
もう一度 俺と戦わせてくれ
今度こそ しとめてやる
I'll bring her down for certain this time.
（皐月）まあ 待て
Be patient.
You must have some plan in mind
（犬牟田(いぬむた)）
喧嘩部を認めたというのには
何か考えがあるのですね？
to have authorized the
Fight Club as you did.
Wait a little longer, and observe.
（皐月）もう少し 見ていろ
ヤツらはこの学園を壊しているのか
Are they bringing down this academy,
or are they being assimilated into it?
それとも飲み込まれているのか
We shall find out soon enough.
すぐにわかる
I see you're back to eating
on your own, Ryuuko.
（鮮血）また１人の食事に
戻ってしまったな 流子
...Not like they'd be here...
いるわけないか
Tell me, Ryuuko.
（鮮血）なあ 流子
Is this really victory?
我々は本当に勝っているのか？
The day when we face off against the Four Devas is here at last!
いよいよ四天王に
挑戦する日が来たわ
If we win this battle,
これに勝てば喧嘩部は
本能字学園の頂点に立つ
the Fight Club will stand supreme on the Student Council!
We'll have all the honor
and luxury we can handle!
名誉も ぜいたくな暮らしも
思いのまま
You're late, Ryuuko!
もう遅いわよ 流子ちゃん
さあ いよいよ決戦よ
The final showdown is here at last!
What's this?
何これ？
My letter of resignation.
（流子）退部届だ
は？ 何 言ってるの？
Huh? What are you saying?!
I'm quitting the Fight Club.
（流子）あたしは喧嘩部をやめる
（マコ）そんな…
You can't!
If you quit now, we'll be
sent back to the slums!
今 流子ちゃんがやめたら
またスラム街に逆戻りよ
I'm okay with that.
それでいいんだ
（マコ）
嫌よ そんなの絶対に嫌！
I'm not! I'm never going back there!
キャー
何？
—What the—
Fight Club President
Mankanshoku Mako!
（皐月）喧嘩部部長 満艦飾マコ
Your Two-Star Ultima Uniform
is inside that wardrobe!
貴様の二つ星極制服が
その中に入っている
My uniform?
（マコ）私の？
If you want to keep your
current social standing and lifestyle,
（皐月）
今の地位と暮らしを守りたければ
纏と戦い そして倒せ
fight and defeat Matoi Ryuuko!
何だと？
Say what?
Defeat Matoi, and I will grant you a Three-Star Ultima Uniform.
纏を倒せば貴様には
三つ星極制服を与えよう
あっ 皐月様…
...Lady Satsuki...
That's playing dirty, Kiryuuin!
鬼龍院 貴様 汚いぞ
The choice of whether to accept or not lies with Mankanshoku.
判断するのは満艦飾だ
You bitch!
てめえ
Life Fiber Synchronize, Godrobe Senketsu!
人衣一体 神衣鮮血
GODROBE
SENKETSU
Don't be so hasty.
慌てるな
貴様の相手は私ではない
I'm not your opponent today.
...Fight Club-Spec...
喧嘩部特化型
Two-Star Ultima Uniform!
二つ星極制服
Fight Club President
Mankanshoku Mako!
喧嘩部部長—
満艦飾マコ！
FIGHT CLUB-SPEC
TWO-STAR
ULTIMA UNIFORM
FIGHT CLUB PRESIDENT
MANKANSHOKU MAKO
They've had a falling out?
（美木杉(みきすぎ)）仲間割れだと？
That's our Lady Satsuki.
She plays dirty.
さっすが皐月様
エグい手を使うわ
Does she, though?
（犬牟田）そうかな
Ryuuko!
（マコ）流子ちゃん 覚悟！
Say your prayers!
（マコ）トォー！
Cut it out, Mako!
（流子）マコ やめろ
I can't! Not now that
we're finally living in luxury!
だって やっとつかんだ
ぜいたくだもん
I can't go back to being poor!
もう貧乏には戻れないもん
Snap out of it, you idiot!
バカ！ 目を覚ませ！
Mr. and Mrs. Mankanshoku!
おじさん！ おばさん！
Damn it!
クソッ
...Mako, what are you...
マコ お前…
Stop! Mako's not in
her right mind right now!
よせ おじさん
今のマコはどうかしてる
If you try to stop her,
you'll put yourselves in danger too!
止めようとすると
あんたたちも危険だ
Huh?
あれ？
What are you standing around for?!
何もたもたしてんだ！
早く流子ちゃんをやっつけろ！
Hurry up and beat the tar out of Ryuuko!
（ガッツ）ガツガツガッツ
（好代）それっ 一気にラッシュよ
Like a bolt of lightning!
（又郎）地獄送りだ
Send her straight to Hell!
って 止めんじゃないのかよ！
You're not gonna try to stop her?!
Sorry, Ryuuko, m'dear.
すまん 流子ちゃん
だが 今の暮らしは捨てられん
But we can't give up the lifestyle
to which we've become accustomed.
Don't worry!
私たち あなたの分まで
幸せになるから
We'll make sure to
enjoy life for you too!
Observe, Matoi! This is
human nature in its purest form!
（皐月）どうだ 纏 これが人間だ
Prosperity leads to greed,
成功は欲望を生み
欲望は破滅を呼ぶ
and greed leads to
their inevitable downfall!
Once they taste those worldly pleasures, they're enslaved by them forever!
だが一度 快楽を知れば
もう抜けられん
They'll become slaves
to this academy I created!
私がつくった学園のとりことなる
ヤツらこそ 服を着た豚
Truly, they are pigs in human clothing!
Pigs which must be tamed by force!
力で屈服させるしかない
豚どもだ！
（マコ）おりゃー
（マコ）フン！
What's the matter, Ryuuko?
（鮮血）どうした？ 流子
I'll be fine like this.
このままでいい
What's she thinking?
（猿投山）
何 考えてやがる あいつ
She's choosing friendship
over her own life?
自分の命より
友情を選ぶというのか
（蹴る音）
（マコ）フン！
Attagirl, Mako!
（薔薇蔵）いいぞ マコ！
（好代）そのまま決めちゃって
Finish her off!
Kill her!
（又郎）やれー
It's all over!
（マコ）とどめだ！
Get her!
（一同）いけー！
（マコ）な… なんで…
Wh-Why?
Why aren't you stopping me?!
なんで止めてくれないのよ！
このままじゃ流子ちゃん
死んじゃうよ
If I keep this up, Ryuuko's gonna die!
Dad, Mom, why aren't
you trying to stop me?!
なのに なんで お父さんも
お母さんも止めてくれないの？
And you call yourselves parents?!
それでも人の親？
Y-You're mad at us?
ぎゃ… 逆ギレ？
When I became club president
and our lives improved,
（マコ）
部長になって 生活 良くなって
みんなキラキラしてると思ってた
I thought our eyes were sparkling.
I thought our whole family was glowing.
家族みんなが輝いてると思ってた
But we weren't, were we?
でも そうじゃなかったの
Was it just a wicked glint?
あれはギラギラしてただけ
Were we just being
blinded by our desires?
欲に目がくらんで
クラクラしてただけ
Was it not the sparkling twinkle of joy, but the gleaming glint of greed?
キラキラじゃなくて
ギラギラのクラクラだったの
（マコ）最低よ！
父ちゃんたちも この私も！
We're the worst!
The whole family's terrible, me included!
So that's the true strength of your Ultima Uniform, Mako.
（流子）これがその極制服の
本当の力だな マコ
You never attacked me all-out.
お前は本気で私を攻撃しなかった
Did you stand there and take that beating because you knew she was holding back?
（鮮血）それがわかっていたから
お前はワザと攻撃を受けたのか？
—Mako was fighting hard, too—
（流子）マコも戦っていた
自分の欲望とな
against her own desires.
ごめんね　ごめんね 流子ちゃん
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Ryuuko!
Take that silly thing off.
脱げ そんなもの
Yeah!
As of today, the Fight Club is disbanded!
（マコ）本日をもって
喧嘩部は廃部します
Fight
Club
Mankanshoku Mako will
go back to being a No-Star!
満艦飾マコは無星に戻ります
Kiryuuin!
鬼龍院！
人間はお前が言うほど弱くない
Humans aren't as weak
as you say they are!
People can suppress their desires through sheer willpower!
欲望も自分の意思で抑え込める
（マコ）流子ちゃん
やっちゃって！
Ryuuko, do it!
With pleasure!
（流子）よっしゃ！
Finishing Move: Thread Stripper!
必殺
TO FIGHT!
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
（美木杉）ほお やるもんだな
That was nicely done.
We're really sorry!
（薔薇蔵たち）すみませんでした
I, Mankanshoku Barazou,
will never live this down!
（薔薇蔵）
この満艦飾薔薇蔵
一世一代の不覚
I'll never act so disgracefully ever again!
（好代）もう二度と—
あんな みっともない
マネしないから
I'm so ashamed for letting my desires get the better of me!
（又郎）
欲に目がくらんで
お恥ずかしいかぎり
We're so very, very sorry!
（薔薇蔵たち）本当に
すみませんでした
（マコ）はっ
We're so sorry!
Pull a stunt like that again, and I
won't be so nice the next time! Got it?
今度 あんなことしたら
容赦しないよ！
Yes, ma'am!
...Well, without further ado...
（薔薇蔵）ということで
（一同）いただきまーす
Let's eat!
Nothing beats your
mystery croquettes, Mom!
（又郎）
やっぱ 母ちゃんの—
よくわからねえ
コロッケが—
いちばん うめえや
You said it! They're the best in Japan!
（薔薇蔵）おう
やっぱり日本一だな
いっぱい食べてね
Eat all you like, boys!
Yeah, these are so good!
う〜ん うまい！
（鮮血）また にぎやかな食事が
戻ってきたな
I see your lively mealtimes
have returned.
ああ このウチはこうでなきゃな
Yeah, this is how
this family should be!
あむ
BACK-ALLEY DOCTOR
MANKANSHOKU
What did you just say?
（猿投山）今 何と言いました？
The fact that all those clubs were defeated by the
lowly Fight Club meant that they were not worthy.
喧嘩部ごときが
他の部長を駆逐するなど—
所詮 そこまでの者だった
ということだ
You're serious, then?
（蛇崩）では本気で？
Enough with your impertinent
questioning, Jakuzure!
（蟇郡）
くだらん質問をするな 蛇崩
Lady Satsuki has never been
anything less than deadly serious!
皐月様が本気でなかったことなど
一度もない
He is correct.
（皐月）そのとおり
I will rebuild Honnouji Academy's order once more from the ground up.
改めて一から本能字学園の
秩序を作り直す
Honnouji Academy will hold
its first ever Naturals Election!
本能字学園 壊惨総戦挙(かいさんそうせんきょ)を
執り行う
HONNOUJI
ACADEMY
FIRST
NATURALS
ELECTION
NEXT TIME!
HONNOUJI ACADEMY NATURALS ELECTION
Wait, surely you didn't just use Matoi
to purge this academy of its undesirables?
ひょっとして あなたは
この学園のうみを出そうとして—
纏を利用した？
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Disciplinary Bureau Chairman
Gamagoori Ira!
（鮮血）
風紀部委員長 蟇郡苛(いら)
GAMAGOORI IRA
A man so loyal that he vows to enroll in driver's school and get his license
鬼龍院皐月の送迎のために—
KIRYUUIN SATSUKI
自動車学校に通い詰め
免許を取るほどの忠誠を誓う男
simply so he can chauffeur
Kiryuuin Satsuki!
LOYALTY
SWEAR
Will his skill behind the
wheel be up to the task?
果たして 彼の運転技術やいかに
HIS SKILL
Next time on KILL la KILL,
"I'll Wipe My Own Tears"!
次回 キルラキル
「俺の涙は俺が拭く」
EPISODE 8
I'LL WIPE MY OWN TEARS